RG 015, Office of Policy and Management
Connecticut State Library
- Series 15. Energy Division, 1960-1990; 31.25 cubic feet
  - Files, 1972-1990; 1996-012
    - Energy Planning, 1973-1980
      - Emergency Natural Gas Act (Box 1)
      - Emergency Petroleum Storage (Box 1)
      - Employment Data (Box 1)
      - Energy Background Papers (Box 1)
      - Energy Conservation Contingency Plans (Box 1)
      - Energy Conservation Devices (Box 1)
      - Energy Extension Service (EES) (Box 1)
      - Energy Policy and Conservation Act (Box 1)
      - Energy Demand (Box 1)
      - Energy Emergency Conservation Act (Box 1)
      - Energy Facility Siting (Box 1)
    - Commissioner Files, 1978-1979
      - Correspondence, 1978 January-June (Box 2)
      - U.S. Department of Energy (Box 2)
      - Memorandums - General Letters on Procedures for State Agencies (Box 2)
      - National Governors' Association (Box 2)
      - Congress (Box 2)
      - Office of Policy and Management (Box 2)
      - CASE (Box 2)
      - American Nuclear Society (Box 2)
      - ABCD, Inc. (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 2)
      - Public Utilities Control Authority (Box 2)
      - CTES (Box 2)
      - Crisis Intervention (Box 2)
      - Gov's Fuel Bank Luncheon (Box 2)
      - CRRA (Box 2)
      - National Energy Act I (Box 2)
      - Set aside (Box 2)
      - Federal legislation (Box 2)
      - Coal (Box 2)
      - CONNSEA (Box 2)
      - Coal Conversion (Box 2)
      - Current correspondence (Box 2)
      - Consultants (Box 2)
      - Home Insulation Task Force (Box 2)
      - OPM Interoffice Memos (Box 2)
      - Hydroelectric Dams (Box 2)
      - Electric Power Research Institute (Box 2)
      - Form 14s (Box 2)
      - Millstone Nuclear Power Plants (Box 2)
      - National Science Foundation (NSF) Bulletins (Box 2)
      - New England regional Commission (NERC) (Box 2)
      - Northeast Utilities Service Company (Box 2)
      - Nuclear Info (Box 2)
      - State Clearinghouse Forms (Box 2)
      - State-Owned Facilities (Box 2)
      - State Legislation (Box 2)
      - Weatherization Program (Box 2)
      - Connecticut Solar Energy Alliance (Box 2)
      - Federal Regional Council of New England (FRC) (Box 2)
    - Administrative Files, 1976-1981
      - Census (Box 3)
      - Center for Energy Policy (Box 3)
      - Center for Environment and Man (Box 3)
      - Census (Box 3)
      - Citizen Groups (Box 3)
      - Class Code Totals (Box 3)
      - Clippings (Box 3)
      - Coal Liquification (Box 3)
      - Other States (Box 3)
      - Conversion comments - position papers (Box 3)
      - Carter's National Energy Act (Box 3)
    - Commissioner Files, 1978-1980
      - Claire Markham (Box 4)
      - Governor's Solar Energy Task Force (Box 4)
      - Energy Budget (Box 4)
      - Department of Administrative Services (Box 4)
      - Department of Education (Box 4)
      - EES (Box 4)
      - Energy Division Press Releases (Box 4)
      - OPM Meeting Reports (Box 4)
      - Power Facility Evaluation Council (Box 4)
      - CT Solar Energy Alliance (CONNSEA) (Box 4)
      - Sunday, 1978 May 3 (Box 4)
      - CT State Lighting Standards for Public Buildings Advisory Committee (Box 4)
      - Urban Action Task Force (Box 4)
      - Coal Conversion (Box 4)
      - Washington (Box 4)
      - Northeast Alliance (Box 4)
      - Schools and Hospitals (Box 4)
      - Gov's Office "Gasahol" correspondence (Box 4)
      - Faith Brenneman (Box 4)
      - Hurt, Susan (Box 4)
      - Rifkin, Rowan H. (Box 4)
      - Establishing a Hydro Position (Box 4)
      - John Helm (correspondence) (Box 4)
      - Correspondence from Ed Butler (Box 4)
      - Correspondence from Lynn Brooks (Box 4)
      - Correspondence from Susan Rumney (Box 4)
      - Rand, Louisa (Box 4)
      - Unfiled material (Box 4)
    - Energy Planning, 1979
      - Petroleum Products Commission (Box 5)
      - Octane/Enf. (Box 5)
      - State Contingency Planning Exercise (AST-3) (Box 5)
      - EECA I&II Fed Plan, 1980 February 7 (Box 5)
      - Fuel Reserve Info/Notes - Lester Green (Box 5)
      - Oak Ridge - ECCA - Outline (Box 5)
      - ECCA II - Management Plan submitted to DOEI, February 27, 1981 (Box 5)
      - EECA II memos (Box 5)
      - Energy Emergency Planning (Box 5)
      - Motor Fuel Revenue Systems (Box 5)
      - Emergency Motor Fuels (Box 5)
      - SAMIS (Box 5)
      - Allocations Gasoline/Oil (Box 5)
      - Gasoline Pricing (Box 5)
      - Monitoring (Box 5)
      - Sales Price Posting Marinas (Box 5)
      - Emergency Energy Conservation Act of 1979 (Box 5)
      - Powerplant and Industrial Fuel Use Act of 1978 (Box 5)
      - Emergency Petroleum Allocation Act of 1973 (Box 5)
      - DOE Report, "Commercial & Industrial Storage of Distillate and Gasoline" (Box 5)
      - EECA Revived (Box 5)
      - EECA II Ph I Management Plan (Box 5)
      - EECA II Extension (Box 5)
      - Emergency Regulations (Box 5)
      - Replacement Sticker Mailing List (Box 5)
    - New England Regional Commission - Northeast Solar Energy Center, 1979-1981 (Box 6)
    - Energy Planning, 1976-1979
      - NESEC organizational (Box 7)
      - Swash Solar Power and Space Heating (Box 7)
      - Passive Solar (Box 7)
      - Universities (Box 7)
      - State Funding (Box 7)
      - New England Solar Energy Association (Box 7)
      - Request for Proposal (Box 7)
      - NESEC Update (Box 7)
      - NESEC Library Files (Box 7)
      - Misc. (Box 7)
      - Solar Commercialization (Box 7)
      - Solar Water Heating Commercialization Plan (Box 7)
      - Public Building Assessment (Box 7)
      - Correspondence (Box 7)
      - NESEC Pre-Imp (Box 7)
      - NESEC Subcontracts (Box 7)
      - NSEC Contract (Box 7)
      - In House reports/memos (Box 7)
      - NERBC - New England River Basin Commission (Box 7)
      - NNECO (Box 7)
      - Northern Tier Pipeline (Box 7)
      - NUSC - Naval Underwater Systems Center (Box 7)
      - NU News Releases (Box 7)
      - NERCOM Solar Proposal (Box 7)
      - Unfiled material (Box 7)
      - NERCOM Regulatory Assistance Program (Box 7)
      - Emergency Planning (Box 8)
      - Emergency Planning (Box 8)
      - Emergency Planning Executive Order #26 (Box 8)
      - Transit Districts, etc (Box 8)
      - Department of Energy Emergency Planning (Box 8)
      - Hartford Simulation Project (Box 8)
      - Standby Rationing Plan (Box 8)
      - Gasoline Rationing Plan Summary (Box 8)
      - Standby Gasoline Rationing Plan Summary (Box 8)
      - EECA Title II (Final Draft) The Management Plan (Box 8)
      - Title I - Standby Rationing SSR (State Ration Reserve) (Box 8)
      - Grant Application EECA Title II - Phase I (Box 8)
      - Federal Emergency Planning (Box 8)
      - EECA - Title II Quarterly Reports (Box 8)
      - Target Program (Box 8)
      - EECA (Box 8)
      - Gov. Report (Box 8)
      - Correspondence Mailing List (Box 8)
      - Emergency Planning Background (Box 8)
      - EECA Draft, 1980 November 20 (Box 8)
      - Data Location (Box 8)
      - EECA Title II - DOE Correspondence (Box 8)
      - EECA Draft, 1980 October 30 (Box 8)
      - Unfiled material (Box 8)
      - Legislation - Emergency (Box 8)
      - Allocations (Box 8)
      - Cox (Box 8)
      - CTES (Box 8)
      - Replacement Sticker Mailing Lists (Box 8)
    - Administrative Files, 1974-1981
      - Long Island Sound Study (Box 9)
      - Misc. Facts & Figures (Box 9)
      - NGA Solar Energy Task Force (SETF) (Box 9)
      - NGC Energy Impact Assistance Task Force (Box 9)
      - NGC Subcommittee on Energy Facility Siting (Box 9)
      - NSF National Science Foundation (Box 9)
      - N.E. Blueprint for Energy Action (Box 9)
      - New England Energy Congress (Box 9)
      - New England Governors' Conference (Box 9)
      - New England Energy Policy (Box 9)
      - Unfiled material (Box 9)
      - Information Requirements (Box 9)
      - FY97 NEEMIS Program Budget (Box 9)
    - Director Files, 1981-1990
      - Low Int. Loan Program Tech. Advisory Comm. (Box 10)
      - Mass. Audubon Intern Program (Box 10)
      - Midwest/NE Coalition (Box 10)
      - Utah Snowbird NASEO meeting, 1988 September 25-26 (Box 10)
      - Canada, P.E.I. NICE's Committee Meetings, 1988 September 13-15 (Box 10)
      - Boston, MA Northeast Gas Market Conference, 1988 June 13-14 (Box 10)
      - Leadership & Communication Course, 1988 May (Box 10)
      - St. John, New Brunswick, NICE "Energy Security" Roundtable, 1988 April 20-22 (Box 10)
      - Aspen, Colorado Least Cost Utility Planning, 1988 April 10-13 (Box 10)
      - New York, NY Policy Committee Meeting & Field Trip, 1988 April 5-6 (Box 10)
      - Washington, D.C. Energy Technology Conference, 1988 February 17-19 (Box 10)
      - Vermont, Burlington Governors' Conference - Superconductivity, 1987 December 15 (Box 10)
      - Greenville, SC DOE/Emergency Steering Group, 1987 December 3-4 (Box 10)
      - St. John's Newfoundland Energy Opportunities in the Nineties, 1987 October 7-8 (Box 10)
      - Sweden Swedish Trade Council, 1987 May 15-23 (Box 10)
      - NICE International Roundtable, 1990 (Box 10)
      - NICE, 1990 (Box 10)
      - NICE Fax Numbers, 1990 (Box 10)
      - NICE Committee Work (Box 10)
      - NICE, 1989 (Box 10)
      - NICE, 1988 (Box 10)
      - NICE, 1987 (Box 10)
      - CACS (Box 10)
      - Coal Project (Box 10)
      - DED (Box 10)
      - EES (Box 10)
      - Energy Survey (Box 10)
      - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 10)
      - Futures Market (Box 10)
    - Misc. Energy Conservation Memos & Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 11)
    - Director Files, 1980-1990
      - Acid Rain (Box 12)
      - Acknowledgements (Box 12)
      - Air Quality (Box 12)
      - Alt. Technology Proposals (Box 12)
      - Amer. Institute of Planners (Box 12)
      - Appliance Efficiency (Box 12)
      - BIOMASS (Box 12)
      - Bottle Bill (Box 12)
      - Bulletin Board Surplus (Box 12)
      - Brookhaven National Laboratories (Box 12)
      - Brandeis University (Box 12)
      - Canada (Box 12)
    - Administrative Files, 1975-1981
      - Energy Impact Asst. (Box 13)
      - Energy Misc. (Box 13)
      - Energy New Briefs (Box 13)
      - Energy Offices (Box 13)
      - Energy Parks (Box 13)
      - Energy Policy (Box 13)
      - ERDA Energy Research and Development Administration (Box 13)
      - Energy Reserve Study (Box 13)
      - Environmental Issues (Box 13)
      - Environ. Law Institute ECP Reports (Box 13)
      - Equalization/Entitlements (Box 13)
      - Unfiled material (Box 13)
    - Director's Files, 1980-1990
      - COGEN Seminar, 1991 April 3 (Box 14)
      - OCS New Orleans Trip, 1991 March 24-29 (Box 14)
      - NICE - Quebec City, 1991 January 29-31 (Box 14)
      - OCS Meeting - Wilmington, NC, 1990 October 30 (Box 14)
      - Meriden, 1990 September 27 (Box 14)
      - CONEG Newark, NJ, 1990 September 21 (Box 14)
      - Alaska Trip, 1990 May 21-29 (Box 14)
      - NICE Conference on Electricity Nova Scotia, 1990 April 24-26 (Box 14)
      - PPC meeting, 1990 April 18 (Box 14)
      - Northeast Gas Mark, 1990 April 11 (Box 14)
      - Northeast International committee Energy, Jackson, NH, 1990 February 1-2 (Box 14)
      - NICE Committee Meeting, Montreal Canada, 1989 October 5-6 (Box 14)
      - RCS Workshop Farmington, CTR, 1989 September 27 (Box 14)
      - Northeast Gas Market Conference, Boston, MA, 1989 September 25-26 (Box 14)
      - DOE State Steering Group Meeting Clemson, SC, 1989 August 28-31 (Box 14)
      - Power Planning Committee Meeting, Portland, ME, 1989 July 11 (Box 14)
      - DOE Emergency Planning Conference Hartford, CT, 1989 June 12-13 (Box 14)
      - NICE South Portland, ME, 1989 April 18-20 (Box 14)
      - CMEEC Meeting, 1989 April 10 (Box 14)
      - Northeast Gas Markets, Boston, MA, 1989 February 8 (Box 14)
      - National Steering Committee, Atlanta, GA, 1989 February 1 (Box 14)
      - NICE, Stockbridge, MA, 1989 January 25-26 (Box 14)
      - Energy Development & the Environment, Boston, MA, 1988 December 1 (Box 14)
      - Oral Test Examiner, Albany NY, 1988 November 21 (Box 14)
      - Can. Policy Committee Meeting, San Diego, CA, 1988 September 28-29 (Box 14)
    - Administrative Files, 1976-1981
      - Gas Curtailment (Box 15)
      - Gasoline Shortage (Box 15)
      - Gasoline (Box 15)
      - Heating Oil Price Survey (Box 15)
      - Hydro Power (Box 15)
      - Industrial Energy Users Forum (Box 15)
      - Industrial (Box 15)
      - I-84 (Box 15)
      - Information for Governor (Box 15)
      - Iranian Situation (Box 15)
      - Kerosene (Box 15)
      - Land Use (Box 15)
      - Legislation (Box 15)
      - Legislation (state proposed) (Box 15)
      - Legislation (federal proposed) (Box 15)
    - Commissioner's Files, 1973-1975
      - Governor's Office Correspondence, 1973 November 9-1974 December 11 (Box 16)
      - Title XX Planning Reports (Box 16)
      - Federal Energy Administration Public Hearings, 1974 December 9 (Box 16)
      - Tri-State Regional Planning Comm., 1975 (Box 16)
      - Title XX, 1975 (Box 16)
      - Council of State Governments - Intergovernmental Environment Conference, Philadelphia, Penn., 1974 May 9-10 (Box 16)
      - New England Energy Management Information System (NEEMIS), 1974 July-December (Box 16)
      - Governor's Office Correspondence, General Memos, etc., 1975 January-September (Box 16)
    - Administrative Files, 1974-1980
      - Alaska Gas Proposals (Box 17)
      - El Paso - Alaskan Natural Gas (Box 17)
      - El Paso Natural Gas (Box 17)
      - Alaskan Natural gas (Box 17)
      - Alcan (Box 17)
      - Artic Gas (Box 17)
      - Artic Gas (Box 17)
      - Algonquin (Box 17)
      - Boundary Gas (Box 17)
      - Natural Gas Crisis, 1977 (Box 17)
      - Natural Gas - Consumption Forecasts (Box 17)
      - Natural Gas Supply/Demand (Box 17)
      - Natural Gas (Box 17)
    - Director's Files, 1980-1990
      - Federal Energy Administration (Box 18)
      - Federal Energy Administration (Box 18)
      - FEA - Region I Energy Information Service (Box 18)
      - FEA - Organization (Box 18)
      - FEA - RFP's (Box 18)
      - FEA - Winter Energy Emergency Planning Task Force (Box 18)
      - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission (Box 18)
      - FPC - Federal Power Commission (Box 18)
      - FRC - Federal Regional Council (Box 18)
      - FRC Energy Resource Task Forces (Box 18)
      - Federal Register Energy Highlights (Box 18)
      - Federal Register Energy News (Box 18)
      - Ford Foundation Energy Policy Project (Box 18)
      - Ford's Program (Box 18)
    - Energy Planning, 1979
      - DOT (Box 19)
      - Reserve Study (Box 19)
      - Emergency Planning Coordinator (Box 19)
      - EECA Standby Plan (Box 19)
      - Misc. Emergency Planning (Box 19)
      - EECA I - Gas Rationing Memos Info (Box 19)
      - EECA I Misc. (Box 19)
      - Federal Gasoline Rationing Program Solicitation (Box 19)
      - Federal gasoline Rationing Plan & Progress Report (Box 19)
      - Emergency Plan Review Correspondence (Box 19)
      - Armory Request (Box 19)
      - Standby Conservation Plan (Box 19)
      - Standby Fed. Energy Conservation Plan, February 7, 1980 Regulations (Box 19)
      - Energy Emergency - Internal Correspondence (Box 19)
      - Emergency Plan Amendment (Draft) (Box 19)
      - Mailing List Energy Emergency Plan for CT (Box 19)
      - Unlabeled material (Box 19)
      - Federal Targets Summary (Box 19)
      - Emergency Plan Amendment, 1980 (Box 19)
      - EECA Planning (Box 19)
      - Executive Summary Emergency Plan, 1975 (Box 19)
      - State Emergency Plan Amendment, 1980 (Box 19)
      - DRAFT Energy Emergency Conservation Plan, 1980 October 30 (Box 19)
      - Regulations (Box 19)
      - Task Force to Monitor Oil Price Changes (Box 19)
      - 2% Earnings Tax on Petroleum Companies (Box 19)
      - Odd/Even (Box 19)
    - Commissioner Files, 1974-1976
      - New England Tank Lining of Connecticut, Inc. (Box 20)
      - New Samaritan Corporation (Box 20)
      - Northeast Utilities (Box 20)
      - Nuclear regulatory Commission, Washington, D.C. 20555 (Box 20)
      - Nuclear Safety Task Force (Box 20)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity - Energy (Box 20)
      - Oil Companies (Major) (Box 20)
      - People and the Sound material (Box 20)
      - New England Regional Commission (Box 20)
        Memorandum of agreements, proposals, grants, contracts
      - New England River Basins Commission (NERBC) (Box 20)
      - Unfiled material (Box 20)
      - NERCOM - Report of the Capitol and Labor Markets, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
    - Administrative Files, 1974-1976 (Box 21)
      - New England Institute (Box 21)
      - New England Natural Resources Center (Box 21)
      - NEPOOL (Box 21)
      - New England Regional Commission (NERCOM), 1976 (Box 21)
      - Winterization Program (NERCOM) Energy (Box 21)
      - New England Regional Commission (NERCOM), 1977 (Box 21)
      - New England Energy Policy, 1976 February-August (Box 21)
      - New England Energy Policy Council (Box 21)
      - New England Energy Policy Task Force (Box 21)
      - New England Fuel Institute (Box 21)
      - New England Governor's Conference (Box 21)
      - New England Governors' / Eastern Canadian Premier's Energy Comm. (Box 21)
      - New England Regional Commission (NERCOM), 1974 June 24-1975 December 17 (Box 21)
      - New England Regional Commission (NERC), 1975 October 22-December 15 (Box 21)
      - New England Regional Commission, Washington, D.C. Highlights of legislation - FLYER (Box 21)
      - New England Regional Commission Durham, New Hampshire Workshop, 1974 November 25 (Box 21)
      - NERCOM Rate Structure Conference (Box 21)
      - 208, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - New England Energy Policy Adopted by NGC, 1975 November 7 (Box 21)
    - Director's Files, 1980-1990
      - Coalition of Northeastern Governors (CONEG), 7 inches (Box 22)
      - Coastal Energy Impact Program (Box 22)
      - Connecticut Farm Bureau (Box 22)
      - Connecticut Marine Trades Association, Inc. (Box 22)
      - Connecticut Petroleum Council (CPC) (Box 22)
      - Connecticut Joint Federation Engineering Exposition and Conference (Box 22)
      - Connecticut Solar Energy Alliance (Box 22)
      - Connecticut Technical Energy Center (Box 22)
      - Conservation (Box 22)
      - Consultants (Box 22)
      - Consumption Forecasting (Box 22)
      - Consumption (Box 22)
      - Conversion Data (Box 22)
      - Continental Offshore Strategic tests (COST) (Box 22)
      - Cos Cob (Box 22)
      - Council on Economic Advisors (Box 22)
      - CSG - Council of State Governments (Box 22)
      - Crude Oil (Box 22)
    - Administrative Files, 1972-1978
      - NEEMIS News (Box 23)
      - New England Power Exchange (Box 23)
      - NEEPS - New England Energy Policy Staff (Box 23)
      - NEPOOL - New England Power Pool (Box 23)
      - NERC Demonstration Projects (Box 23)
      - New England Public Utilities Commissioners (NERCOM), 3 inches (Box 23)
    - Director's Files, 1980-1990
      - Unfiled material (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous - Eastern Canadian Energy Paper (Box 24)
      - National Research Council (NRC) (Box 24)
      - National Association of Van Pool Operators (NAVPO) (Box 24)
      - NU/EEI Pilot Project (Box 24)
      - Oil Company Mergers (Box 24)
      - OPM House Committee (Box 24)
      - PPVR Misc. (Box 24)
      - Program Budget Proj. (Box 24)
      - Publicity (Box 24)
      - Burner Tune Up Program (Box 24)
      - Conn. School Finance Advisory Panel (Box 24)
      - Conn. School Finance Advisory Panel (Box 24)
      - Planning & Energy Policy (Box 24)
      - Winterization (Box 24)
- Series 16. Secretary, 1980-1998; 31 cubic feet
  - Anthony V. Milano, 1980-1990
    - Subject Files
      - 1978-1979 & 1979-1980 OPM Annual Reports, 1983 & 1987 Reports on "Organization of State Government", 1983 & 1988 Council of State Governments, 1983 Budget & Legislation, Budgeting Process, & miscellaneous correspondence regarding budget issues, 1988 UConn Health Center, AIDS, & Bonding. (Box 1)
      - Policy Issues for the 1980s, OPM Under Secretaries Meetings 1980-1983, 1981 Budget Issues, 1982 High Technology, 1982 Bradley Airport, Budget & Mental Health, & 1984 Job Training Coordinating Council. (Box 2)
      - 1982 OPM Comprehensive Planning, Employment & Training, Energy, Intergovernmental Relations, Management & Evaluation, and the Departments of Administrative Services, Aging, Children & Youth Services, Corrections, Economic Development, Education, Environmental Protection, Health Services, Higher Education, Housing, Human Resources, Income Maintenance, Judicial, Labor, Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Motor Vehicles, Public Safety, Revenue Services, and Transportation. (Box 3)
      - 1983 OPM Budget & Financial Management, Budget Division Audit Reviews and Business Office. (Box 4)
      - 1983 Infrastructure Task Force, Management Advisory Council (MAC), National Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO), National Governors Association (NGA), Educational Equity Study Committee & general (Box 5)
      - 1983 & 1984 Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA), 1984 Federal Emergency Management Act (FEMA), IGR, Management & Evaluation, Energy, & general correspondence. (Box 6)
      - 1984 Reorganization & Capitol Budgeting, Legislature, & Bonding; 1985 Comptroller, Attorney General, Governor's Office, Management Advisory Council (MAC), Municipal Infrastructure Trust Fund, CT Health & Educational Facilities Authority (CHEFA), National Governors Association (NGA), Uncas Advisory Committee Budget Process, Statewide Payroll & Accounting Systems Design Project, Comptroller's Office, & sales tax correspondence. (Box 7)
      - 1984 Transportation Infrastructure Renewal Program, Budget and Financial Management, Comprehensive Planning, Unemployment Compensation, Auditors' Reports, Affirmative Action, Business Office, Management Adviwory Council (MAC), State Leasing of Buildings, and Personnel Issues including Agency Reduction Options. (Box 8)
      - 1985 Health Care issues, Objective Job Evaluations, Municipalities, Bonding, Transportation, Budget Preparation, Legislation, Auditors' Reports, OPM's Business Office, and the Job Training Partnership Act. (Box 9)
      - 1985 Connecticut Resource Recovery Authority (CRRA), Municipalities, Energy, Criminal Justice, UNCAS, Data Processing, the State Suggestion Program, Management Advisory Council (MAC), and the Departments of Environmental Protection, Education, Income Maintenance, Mental Health, and Mental Retardation. (Box 10)
      - 1986 OPM Budget-Audit Reports, Business Office, Comprehensive Planning, Energy, Intergovernmental Relations, Justice Planning, and Management & Evaluations. (Box 11)
      - 1986 Departments of Administrative Services, Aging, Agriculture, Corrections, Economic Development, Education, Health Services, Higher Education, Housing, Human Resources, Income Maintenance, Labor, Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Motor Vehicle, Public Safety, Revenue Services, Transportation, and the Attorney General, Comptroller's Office, CT Higher Education Student Loan Authority (CHESLA), and CT Housing Finance Authority (CHFA). (Box 12)
      - 1986 Governor's Office, Management Advisory Council (MAC), Minutes of Meetings, Miscellaneous Correspondence, National Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO), National Governors Association (NGA), and Publications (2). (Box 13)
      - 1986 Transportation Accountability Board (TAB), Treasurer's Office; 1982 Office of Policy and Management, Budget Division, and Business Office. (Box 14)